<resources>
    <string name="app_name">My Application</string>
    <string name="button1text">Click to see magic</string>
    <string name="buttont2ext">ScorllViewActicity</string>
    <string name="imgdesc1">harry</string>
    <string name="imgdesc2">hermione</string>
    <string name="imgdesc3">ron</string>
    <string name="paragraph1">Kotlin is a statically typed,
                 general-purpose programming language developed
                 by JetBrains, that has built world-class IDEs
                 like IntelliJ IDEA, PhpStorm, Appcode, etc.
                 It was first introduced by JetBrains in 2011
                 and a new language for the JVM. Kotlin is
                 object-oriented language, and a “better language”
                 than Java, but still be fully interoperable
                 with Java code. Kotlin is sponsored by Google,
                 announced as one of the official languages for
                 Android Development in 2017.
                 Advantages of Kotlin language:
                 Easy to learn – Basic is almost similar to java.
                 If anybody worked in java then easily understand
                 in no time. Kotlin is multi-platform – Kotlin is
                 supported by all IDEs of java so you can write
                 your program and execute them on any machine
                 which supports JVM. It’s much safer than Java.
                 It allows using the Java frameworks and libraries
                 in your new Kotlin projects by using advanced
                 frameworks without any need to change the whole
                 project in Java. Kotlin programming language,
                 including the compiler, libraries and all the
                 tooling is completely free and open source and
                 available on github. Here is the link for
                 Github https://github.com/JetBrains/kotlin
                 Applications of Kotlin language:
                 You can use Kotlin to build Android Application.
                 Kotlin can also compile to JavaScript, and making
                 it available for the frontend. It is also designed
                 to work well for web development and server-side
                 development.Kotlin is a statically typed, general-purpose
                 programming language developed by JetBrains that
                 has built world-class IDEs like IntelliJ IDEA,
                 PhpStorm, Appcode, etc. It was first introduced
                 by JetBrains in 2011.Kotlin is object-oriented
                 language and a better language than Java, but still
                 be fully interoperable with Java code. A constructor
                 is a special member function that is invoked when
                 an object of the class is created primarily to initialize
                 variables or properties. A class needs to have a constructor
                 and if we do not declare a constructor, then the compiler
                 generates a default constructor.
                 Kotlin has two types of constructors –
                 Primary Constructor
                 Secondary Constructor
                 A class in Kotlin can have at most one primary
                 constructor, and one or more secondary constructors.
                 The primary constructor
                 initializes the class, while the secondary
                 constructor is used
                 to initialize the class and introduce some extra logic.</string>
    </resources>